I never dreamed before
I'm gonna knock the door
into the world of perfect free
(You ain't no lonely!)
You're gonna say I'm lying
I'm gonna get the chance
I thought a chance is far from me
(You ain't no lonely!)
I was made to hit in America
(I was made to hit in America)
You are the sun, you are the star
(To me, forever)
I was made to hit in America
(I was made to hit in America)
Sorrow is what I hate
but it's grown my sensations.
Regrets taught me how
to make any hard decisions.
Peace is always by my side
but I've never felt it once.
Love is not the word only
for the sweet romance.
Well I'm scared, I'm scared,
I'm scared, I'm scared to death.
Well, I didn't expect this.
It's Malcolm's fault.
That punk from Newark.
He just went back to the hotel
without saying anything.
There are plenty of Mongolian Chop squads.
On this planet...
...they're one of those shitty
bands that don't make no money.
They fucking suck.
I saw the letter from
Uncle Davis by accident.
I can't believe what I read.
It said, "To Ryusuke Minami...
The man who will inherit
the legend of Sonny Boy."
My uncle says that to everybody.
What?
But it is the first time he says
he actually is gonna hand
over the Lucille to them.
That's a first.
Recalling my torn broken,
aching heart of these long days.
And all the memories I wanted
to forget for making leaps.
Recalling, breaking, aching, crying,
making sure to me.
And I take all and grin
at my future on the way.
Sorrow is what I hate
but it's grown my sensations.
Regrets taught me how
to make any hard decisions.
Peace is always by my side
but I've never felt it once.
So that's how they get the audience.
Peace is always by my side
but I've never felt it once.
Boss, that little bastard...
Love is not the word
only for the sweet romance. Yeah.
Well I'm scared, I'm scared,
I'm scared, I'm scared to death.
And I'm scared to keep on
going on my way. Yeah.
Well I'm scared, I'm scared,
I'm scared, I'm scared to death.
Huh? What's up?
Well I'm scared, I'm scared,
I'm scared, I'm scared to death.
-You know this song?
-It's the first time I'm hearing it...
And I'll tell myself
I'm special till the end.
-But it's a really great song.
-Yeah.
And I'll tell myself
I'm special till the end.
Wow!
Koyuki-kun...Saku-chan...
I don't give my heart to no one
cause I don't wanna waste my time.
Koyuki-kun...Saku-chan...
I don't give my heart to no one
cause I don't wanna waste my time.
I tried to love this loneliness
to slip out of lonesome hole.
Hey, do you hear that?
They're calling for us!
It turned out to be...
an awesome live.
But Koyuki is amazing.
He went up on stage all alone.
I couldn't have done that.
-I'm not that brave.
-All of you...All of you came.
That's why I could do it.
I wouldn't have had such a
great time all by myself.
Alright! Let's do an encore!
Are you okay, Koyuki?
Uh-huh...
But can I take three minutes to rest?
Hey, are you gonna
keep your audience waiting?!
Koyuki's too exhausted.
Let him rest.
Hey, Ryusuke...
I'm outta here.
I thought this time
we'd have a permanent band.
Ryusuke-kun!
Yo, what's up, Koyuki?
-Ahh...
-Hey!
You see? Watch out!
You're exhausted.
Don't force yourself.
You okay?
I wanted to tell you...
Ryusuke-kun...Thank you.
Be seeing you, Koyuki.
Wow! Fireworks! How touching!
Huh, Eiji-kun?
Huh?
Yoshito...you...
Maho won't answer.
Main stage, 8,900 people.
Second Stage, 980 people.
And Third Stage, 8,100 people...
and growing steadily!
It's unbelievable,
but if this keeps up,
Stage 3 will turn it around and win.
The main stage keeps
losing spectators...
and I don't see
the crowd lessening.
But we've got trouble on Stage 3.
The crowd has grown tremendously,
but BECK hasn't
come back for an encore.
Huh? Why?!
Well, I...
Encore! BECK! BECK!
-Come out!
-Give us an encore!
-Encore! Encore!
-Hey, that's...
-No way!
It's the vocalist for BECK!
-Hey, he's running away! Hey! Wait!
-Wait! Wait!
Maho!
Let's go!
-Koyuki!
-Maho!
No one can follow us!
No!
Koyuki, you're too fast!
You were watching?
Uh-huh.
After all, Koyuki...
Koyuki...
That was an awesome performance.
Seriously, I was blown away.
Koyuki...you're so cool.
This is gonna be our final live.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
The next day, many great
bands performed on stage.
Hey, Koyuki...Hurry it up.
Uh-huh.
Where's Chiba-kun?
He's going home by train.
Oh...
He said he wants to be alone.
I heard that a band named
BECK was great yesterday.
Oh yeah?
I really, really wanted to see that.
Koyuki!
Oh, sorry!
Tomorrow and the day after
and the day after that...Time will pass.
Regardless of what happens to BECK.
Saku, take a look at this.
Wow! Awesome!
A month and a half has passed
since that live performance.
What am I doing?
Yukio, telephone!
Who is it?
Some lady named Sato.
O-Ouch!
Koyuki-kun, do you have some
time tomorrow afternoon?
Huh? Tomorrow?
In front of the station
by that dog. At one p.m.
BECK's live performance
has become a legend.
Oh...
-I saw the magazine.
-Lots of things are being said,
but it's impossible to get a true count
from that huge mass of people.
Why did you want to see me?
There's someone
who wants to meet you.
Who is it?
You'll be shocked.
Welcome, Yukio.
Let me get straight
to the point today.
I'd like to talk about your
solo debut in the United States.
Uh...Is this...
He's Mr. Leon Sykes.
He wants you to make
a solo debut across America.
Don't you mess with me baby.
Everybody knows I'm here.
All I've got to say, yeah,
got my mind made up.
This is a great guitar.
I'll let you think about it.
Great, man!
We'll meet over and over again
to talk about this project.
We released five gold discs
from RJ Label last year.
Wow! Malcolm and Fat Jimmy
and Danger Soul!
They're all at the top
of the charts right now!
I'm sorry.
I can't accept your proposal.
I'm returning the guitar, too.
What?!
H-Hey Koyuki-kun!
Ah...I'll call you back later!
Koyuki-kun!
Boss! You want me to get him?
Hey, do you understand
what you're doing?!
Huh? Understand what?
Cripes! This is the chance of a lifetime!
It's never going to
come around again!
-I can't believe this!
-Things are so boring lately.
No one would notice
if I were gone.
Ryusuke-kun...
What? Ryusuke Minami
has disappeared?
Yeah, Boss.
Find him. And take him out!
Yeah.
But I guess we gotta take care
of that kid from yesterday, too, huh?
You want me to put him on his back?
I've never heard that kind of music...
Like "Don't You Mess with Me."
W-What'd you say, Boss?
I'll never be part of a band again!
-Huh?! That's...
-Huh!?
I'm gonna use this shop
to train myself and learn
with the goal of opening
a chain of ramen shops!
Taira says he wants
to try a new band, too.
But this ramen is pretty bad.
-You should find
another shop to train at.
-Shut up!
Please join our group,
Typhoon Stones, as a guitarist!
Sorry, but I must refuse.
There's a month till
our live performance.
So please think it over. Please!
Really, think about it!
Please say yes!
Why won't you join them
to help them out?
Hmm...
Koyuki, I wanna talk to you.
Huh? Saku...
I'm used to it.
I mean, grade school,
middle school, high school.
This will be the fifth time.
But this time is harder than the rest...
changing schools like this.
Saku!
It's still two months away.
But I wanted to let you know first.
Saku...
Oh yeah...I want to
tell you one more thing.
What is it?
It may be too soon
to bring this up...
But I may quit music after this.
But...
But Koyuki...
You must never quit music!
Saku...
I want you to write more
songs like "Slip Out"...
...that truly moved people's hearts.
What're you saying?!
Saku, you're the one
who mustn't quit music!
I've learned so much...
...from you...
Koyuki...
Hey Tanaka...You were on tonight!
Next time again, 'kay?
Yeah, I'm amazed.
See ya!
Huh? Aren't you coming
to the wrap party?
I was gonna try to convince him...
...to be a permanent member
of the Typhoon Stones.
It's been a while,
so I was nervous.
Yeah, you haven't played
since Grateful Sound.
Yeah...
I helped out with a band
a couple of times,
but I got nervous, too.
But...something's missing.
Something's totally missing.
'Cuz I really had a taste of it.
That BECK was a really special band.
Sorry to keep you waiting!
It's your last day, Saku...
So let's really party up!
Yeah!
Hey Saku, not bad!
Wow!
Hey Koyuki! Get a strike!
-No way!
-Oh no!
Yes! Six wins in a row!
Yay!
Hey, let's change teams.
I want to be with Saku!
Darn it! One more game!
Huh?!
Isn't their ramen great?
-Really!
-Didn't I tell you?
Okay, on to the next stop!
Umm...I have curfew, so...
-Huh? So soon?
I'm sorry!
It's dangerous for a girl alone...
Don't worry. I'll see her home.
So long, Koyuki.
Take care.
-It's kinda sad.
-Yeah...
Chiba-kun is training to be
a ramen shop owner, right?
And Taira-kun just joined up with
the popular Indies band as a bassist.
And Ryusuke is missing.
Seems like BECK is no more.
Brrr...cold!
Are you all right?
You sound kinda nasal.
See you around, Koyuki.
Don't catch cold!
Huh? Maho?
Saku!
It's soo cold outside!
The weather forecast
calls for snow tomorrow.
Oh yeah?
-Let's eat.
-Yeah.
Oh! Potato chips! Ew!
Kimchi flavored!?
So tonight, too, you just
walked her home and that's all?
Unfortunately, we've never
even held hands.
Hmm...
How far have you gone with Maho?
Huh? I...
I told you before...
Then there's been no progress
since the day of Grateful Sound?
Hey...let's stop!
This was our first live!
Man, it sounds awful!
Remember, Chiba-kun was under
the wrong impression...
And he got it!
-Oh well...
-Saku...
I'm gonna go.
-I'll walk with you.
-Okay.
-Hey Koyuki...
-Yeah?
Huh?!
It's snowing!
It's freezing!
Cold!
Cold!!
Damn, it's cold!
It's so cold!
Cold!
-Cold!
Well good-bye, Koyuki.
Take care, Saku.
I'll find a part-time job and save
enough money to live on my own.
I'll convince my parents
and come back in the spring.
In order to revive BECK
with the original members...
I'll quit school and come back!
Uh-huh.
Take care!
You too, Saku!
That was a great piece.
What's your name?
-Yuji Sakurai -a senior in Group 2.
-You're...
I wanted to give this to you.
It's the Dying Breed's
live concert in Germany.
Did you read the interview
of Eddy Lee in Guitar World?
There are two types
of people in this world.
Clever people and obedient people.
Clever people think that the world moves
because of laws and morals created by man.
They think it's everything.
But I don't bother with any of that.
Isn't Eddy amazing?
So, you're in a band?
Koyuki!
Full moon sways
Gently in the night of one fine day
What a fool
I don't know 'bout tomorrow
What it's like to be
Ah...
I was fool
Couldn't let myself to go
Even though I feel
The end
Full moon sways
Smiling in my arms for all those years
Next week: 'America'
Our journey continues.
Although it's the end
of my ramen shop.